FROM ME TO YOU
RUMORS
- Sawako, go ahead and take your bath now.
- Okay.
- Oh, ' Sawako, how has school been? Good?
- Uh...
I- It's been fun.
She's always told us it was fun whenever
we asked before... but that face tells me
- she really means it.
- She's sure excited... huh?
Could it be love?
- Sawako... My little Sawako...
- Darling what are you doing?! You
need to pull yourself together!
I'm so happy.
Experiencing this much happiness ' is so
intense, it almost makes me forget how my
- life was before.
- This one's all mine.
Uh... I don't really know what that
meant, but... For some reason, it made me
feel really happy. I've had so many good
moments lately, it's possible I'm using up
all the luck I'll ever
get to have in my life.
But even if I am, I'm still happy.
What? No way!
Yoshida? ' That girl
with the narrow eyes?
Yeah, her! I heard she was completely out
of control when she was in middle school.
She'd make the teacher cry all the time
and punch all the boys in the face and--
Give me some credit, girls. I've done so
many cooler things than that, you know?
Plus, ' my eyes aren't that
narrow so you're making that up.
Yano, right? So it
wasn't just the way she looks.
Yeah! A hundred guys is
crazy, let alone in middle school.
You really think there a hundred
guys out there capable of satisfying me?
But, if those guys do exist,
then you should bring them to me.
This sucks! The real Legend of
Chizuru Yoshida is way cooler!
- That's just how rumors work.
- They're so full of it! My eyes
aren't that narrow ' are they?
They're at least more narrow than you seem
to think they are. But man, do they love
spreading bullcrap around like
fertilizer. Not to mention that Sadako
rumor...
- What do you think?
I'm asking you where this
bullcrap started! What's the source?
Sa... Sadako.
That's what I heard!
Sadako's trying to make herself popular
and she's using you, Yano and especially
Kazehaya in order to do it.
That's literally impossible!
But should we go ask her about it
anyway? -And so... ' The ramen there was
like... -Mmm-hm.
Hi, Yano, Yoshida. M- morning.
Morning, Sadako! Hey, did you ever hear
how I punched all the guys in my class
before?
And for me... did you know I was a huge
nympho and went through a hundred guys in
middle school already.
Ah... That's so cool. You
both are so accomplished!
- Pure!
Oh, uh... So Yoshida, if
you'd like, this is for you.
Huh? What's this?
I made some notes last night. They should
cover all the midterm's key points. And I
' hope they'll help you.
T-The purest bean! I
promise to put it to good use.
Um, Yano?
Hm?
I've been wanting to practice my ghost
stories, and I thought of renting some
movies as reference. Would you mind
telling me some of your favorite or
recommended titles?
- Purest of beans!
So those notes Yoshida...
Could ' I ' copy?
- Me too! I'll give you some brushes!
- Same here!
Huh? That cool?
Of course!
Yessss!
It really does mean the world
to me... when I can help others...
- The purest bean to ever exist!
- Ryu.
- M-Morning, Sanada.
Morning.
Kazehaya's... running late today.
You don't believe me, do you?
I ' I saw them last night,
really! All these little old men!
Pin... Did you forget that I'm
supposed to be in class right now?
Last night, it was
when I was drinking sake...
There were so many of them! Running in
circles around my cup. They wouldn't stop,
it made my head spin. Round and round,
round and round, round and round, and
around...
Then, as if that weren't bad enough,
one by one, they climbed into the cup!
- Pin... Pin!
- Look. I'm late, class already started.
And something like
that takes... ' teamwork.
I'm leaving.
So, ' how're things going?
With that Kuronuma girl, I mean.
Why bring her up?
Ever since I looked her in the eyes,
strange things have been happening. -You
sit right next to her, so you must know
all about it, don't you? How she puts
curses on-- -I only believe
what I see with my own eyes.
And the Kuronuma that I see
is positive and sweet too.
So, uh... ~Are the two of you dating?
- Wh-
- W- what're you so worked up
about? Wait, you mean -?!]
Stop! Don't you say
another word about it or else!
That's it. I'm leaving now.
Woah. Seriously?
He must be into some pretty weird stuff.
So, you know...
- Morning.
Morning.
Uh G'morning.
You were late.
Pin was forcing me to listen
to his little old men story.
The what?
- I dunno.
- His forehead is showing.
She seems... normal.
Even though I went and
said all that stuff yesterday.
His forehead... I I
want to see it once more.
Are the two of you dating?
- This is bad... I can't even look at her.
- His forehead... Too bad.
Along with the abundant happiness I've
been feeling... I can sense my heartbeat
increasing each day.
- Hey.
- I wonder how everyone else is feeling.
Sorry for the wait.
Do they... enjoy hanging out with me?
I sure hope they do.
That would make me even happier.
Up until now, I always thought it was
just a given that I wouldn't have anyone
- around me.
- Tasty, right?
Hm.
- Nope.
- So I've never had a reason to
- think about these sorts of things.
- Hey!
Ever since that day, I've had all these
feelings I never knew of before. My
heart's overflowing.
I want to treasure them.
Like I've been given a
gift... for the very first time.
Yano! Yoshida!
' So, uh... It's just that...
- There've been some rumors about you
- Yeah... so I've heard.
It seems like they're
getting more intense lately.
Yoshida, ' they said you knocked
over an old man and made him gush blood.
Well, I mean I've helped up a
grandpa who's fallen before, but...
And Yano ' they say you hook up
schoolgirls with sugar daddies.
- 'Disgusting!!
- ... ' We don't believe a word of
- it ' but that isn't the problem.
- It's about who's spreading these rumors.
Kuronuma. It's her.
- There's no way!
- That's a lie!
We were wondering why all these rumors
suddenly popped up... and we started to get
- worried.
- Isn't that totally awful?
Yeah, she's ice cold, spreading a
rumor like that. Right?! I can't believe...
Lately, it feels like everyone's
even more afraid of me than usual.
Sadako!
- Hey Shino!
- Here.
Hey, not sure if you know, but
there's been a lot of rumors about you.
That rumor about me having psychic
powers... It must've finally reached Shino.
Well, I think... misunderstandings can
be pretty difficult to clear up, so...
I see. Makes sense!
It should be obvious... Sadako would never
spread bad rumors about her friends. It's
unthinkable.
But I don't feel like these sorts of
things really affect me much anymore.
After all, the people I have
around me are so good to me.
Actually ' you seem a lot more
chilled out than you did before, Sadako.
Why are they all goin' on
about Sadako this and Sadako that?
You know why. We stick out like
sore thumbs... both us and Sadako.
I'm used to us getting that crap, ' but
with Sadako, it's an entirely different
- type of rumor.
- But I'm happy for you.
You were able to make friends. I
believe their names are Yano and Yoshida?
Huh? Th- They're not my friends!
- Oh, I just assumed...
- Wha...
There's more. ' Right?
- There you are. ' Come with me.]
-' Hey, wait...
- So they aren't your friends?
- No...
I don't think so... Aren't friends more
like the way Yano and Yoshida are with
- each other?
- Let go of me already!
Are you listening?! Let go!
Just watching them interact day to day,
I always get this underlying sense that
they love each other.
So yeah. ' that's why I don't ' feel
qualified to use the word "friend".
But, either way I... I
really like them... both of them.
So if one day we can become friends...
I can't express how nice that'd be.
Huh?! The baseball
team's... secret training plan?
Pass it to Ryu for me.
Give me break!
- Ow...
- Ugh! People suck today! Every
- single one of them is pissing me off!
- Ya need to chill, Chizu.
But th- they're not my friends!
I know what we heard Sadako say, but we
still haven't talked to her about it, and
until then, we don't know what she meant.
On the other hand, I guess if anyone asks
if we're friends with Sadako,
we don't have a clear answer.
You're right.
Uh what?
I wonder what happened.
They're usually laughing together...
Sadako, come chat with us over here, kay?
Huh?
They seem... kind of upset...
I'm gonna ask something big. so please be
one hundred percent honest with us. It's
just... well the two of us want you
to know that we like you Sadako.
How do you feel?
Do you also like us... or?
W- Well, I wouldn't say "like", but...
- Instead of "like," I'd say moooore, um--
- Got it.
We ' understand.
Sorry ~ For bothering you.
Y'you're not...
We barely talked about anything... Was I
able to help them understand how I felt?
Is that how these things work?
The two of us want you
to know that we like you.
I should be... over the moon right now.
But seeing Yano and Yoshida from
behind like this... I can tell they're
upset.
...For some reason it's
making me feel sad too.
I wonder if there's anything I
can do to help them feel better?
So after that, she got carried away and
even started using Yoshida and Yano as her
- backup.
- Backup?
Not just them, she's even
taking advantage of Kazehaya.
Kazehaya too?
- T- They must be a powerful person.
- Seriously? Sadako's doing that?!
W-when did my reputation go
from Sadako to gang boss?!
Those dark rumors about Yano and
Yoshida are pretty extreme, huh?
Dark rumors? About being my backup?
That's why they looked so upset
earlier. They must've been hurting.
Well, it's all Sadako's fault.
Uh-huh. Because she's always
hanging around and latching onto them.
Poor Kazehaya too.
If Sadako keeps hovering around him like
this, she'll end up ruining his
reputation.
This is... my fault?
When it comes down to it... Yano and
Yoshida are just really nice. It's in
their nature... to treat me
with the pure kindness they do.
But...
It's because she's
always latching on to them...
So I'm actually hurting everyone
because I'm around them too much?
And if I stay friends with them... will
that keep hurting Yano and Yoshida?... ... And
then Kazehaya someday too?
Oh yeah! Did you hear the
story about the little old men?
- Yeah, ' I have too.
- Seriously?!
- Yeah. They looked just like Zen.
- Just like Zen.
You're kidding!
- We are!
Is it better... if I'm not around them?
Am I not allowed to stay with them?
What's with the face, were you
up all night crying or something?
You're one to talk, Yano-chin. You
look like you just finished pulling an
all-nighter!
Yano-chin?
Hmm?
Those stupid rumors about us... Do
you think Sadako actually spread them?
I honestly don't know what to believe
anymore At least not after hearing her
reply yesterday.
Well, the one thing we know for sure
after talking to her yesterday is that she
- doesn't like us, so...
- I mean, you did straight up
ask her, "Do you like us?"
If she had replied right away with, "Yes,
I do," it'd be clear she wasn't spreading
rumors about us. That would have made all
the difference, right? Then you'd believe
her?
I didn't think Sadako would ever spread
rumors like that... I was 100% sure. But
now, I'm worried that...
there's a possibility it's true.
I want to believe that Sadako would never
spread any rumors. Thinking this way makes
me... hate myself.
G- Good morning.
- Good morning.
Their eyes are red.
I'm sorry.
- Huh?
It was me... who was making
you two upset, wasn't it?
What's ' that mean?
- So I thought I'd go and see!
- I'll be in class!
- Wai... Sadako!
- Not great!
Sadako just... apologized.
But what do you think she meant by that?
You don't think... Sadako
really spread those rumors?
Hey! You can't say that! Knock it off!
- I hate that idea just as much as you!
- Hold on... was that about yesterday?
Was she saying, ' "I'm
sorry that I don't like you"?
Both of those options are are horrible.
Yeah, ' this sucks.
Did I just have a ' big head? I thought
we were really important to Sadako. ' I
really don't get it.
I thought so too. ' I mean, she
definitely seemed like she really liked
- us.
- I knew they were hurt, but it was so
much worse than I imagined... I'm sorry
Yano, Yoshida.
I need to find the people spreading the
rumors and clear the air! Yano and Yoshida
aren't my backup... It's
nothing like that at all.
...They're just really nice... I have
to tell everyone. I've cleared up
misunderstandings before...
I'm sure I can do it again!
I've looked all over... but I can't find
whoever could be spreading the rumors.
Listen... this will come up in the
midterms too, so it's important you commit
it to memory.
I want them to be themselves again. The
bubbly, always smiling and laughing Yano
and Yoshida that I remember.
I can't cry now... not when I'm the
one that made them want to cry.
Kuronuma! Wait!
- Hey, Did I do something?
- I, uh have something I need to do, so...
In class ' you were crying.
And lately, you've been avoiding me.
Have I hurt you or something? Because if
I've done something to make you hate me,
- then please tell me!
- N-Not at all! Kazehaya, you
haven't done anything to me.
But...
Please...
Know that ' no matter what happens in
the future, I will never ever hate you.
And that'll never, ever change...
no matter what lies ahead for us.
- Kuronuma.
- I know right, isn't that so stupid!
I dunno, you're a little too relaxed
considering we got exams comin' up.
Eh, whatever. It's too late
to do anything at this point.
I am so sorry.
Kuronuma!
Kazehaya... I'm sorry.
No matter what happened, what
people said, you never abandoned me.
But... if I'm around you, I'll
only cause problems for you.
I know... I'd be a burden...
But I don't want to avoid him
I know I should stay away.
But I want to stay by his side.
Am I doing the right thing by staying away
from them? Or am I wrong?] I don't know...
I don't know!]
I don't know... what I'm supposed to do.
The people important to me. And the
things... I can do for them right now.
Next time: "Determination"